A Guide to the Pamela Webb Architectural Collection, 1950-2009
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Professional Papers and Files
  - Projects
    - Greene Project, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Greenfield Health System, Portland, OR, 2001 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Griffith / Dickey House II, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Griffith / Dickey Landscape Design, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Griffith / Dickey Remodel, Portland, OR, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Griffith / Dickey Remodel—Financial, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Grove Project, undated (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Hall Renovation, Troutdale, OR, 1996 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Hanchett-Monk Bathroom Renovation, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Hansen Renovations, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Havurah Shalom, Portland, OR, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 6:12-20)
    - Havurah Shalom—Bernalee Cutler, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:21)
    - Havurah Shalom—Emily Simon, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:22)
    - Havurah Shalom—Harwin Studies, Portland, OR, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 6:23)
    - Hearing / Lawshe Remodel, Portland, OR, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 6:24-27)
    - Hendrix Streb Renovations, Portland, OR, 2004 (Box-folder 6:28)
    - Holmes Project, Portland, OR, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 6:29)
    - Illinsky Lot, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 6:30)
    - Ingersoll / Dayton Residence Remodel, Portland, OR, 1989 (Box-folder 6:31)
    - Innersound Project, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:32)
    - Jacob's Properties, Portland, OR, 1997 (Box-folder 6:33)
    - Johnson Country House, West Linn, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:34-35)
    - Johnson Country House—Signed Contract, West Linn, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:36)
    - Johnson Country House—Specifications, West Linn, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 6:37)
    - Johnson / Wilson Addition, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 6:38)
    - Jones Kitchen, Hallandale, FL, 1999 (Box-folder 6:39)
    - Kaer House, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 6:40)
    - Kalisvaart & Co, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 6:41)
    - Kalisvaart Office Furniture, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 6:42)
    - Karlin Dental Office, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 6:43)
    - Kaye Cabin, Hood River, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 6:44)
    - Kaye Cabin—Communications, Hood River, OR 1991 (Box-folder 6:45)
    - Kaye Cabin—Declaration of Restrictions, Hood River, OR, 1977 (Box-folder 6:46)
    - Kilbourne Project, undated (Box-folder 6:47)
    - Kilston Residence, Cottage Grove, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 6:48)
    - King Job, undated (Box-folder 7:1)
    - Kirsch Project [on Greenhills], Portland, OR, 2001 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Klapper / Hickey Cabin / Wood Deck, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Klapper / Hickey Kitchen, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Klute Project, Portland, OR, c. 1978 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Koop House, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 7:6-7)
    - Koop House [Manchester Site], Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Koop House Presentation, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - Krener Project, 1995 (Box-folder 7:10)
    - Kuehnel Project, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Kuhn Project, undated (Box-folder 7:12)
    - Langford House, Portland, OR, 1994 (Box-folder 7:13)
    - Langford House—Financial, Portland, OR, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 7:14)
    - Langford House—Trellis, Portland, OR, 1994 (Box-folder 7:15)
    - Lansky Project, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 7:16)
    - Legacy Homes, 1985-1986; undated (Box-folder 7:17-18)
    - Legal Aid, Portland, OR, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 7:19)
    - Leland Project, Portland, OR, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 7:20)
    - Levy / Maranze Remodel, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 7:21)
    - Levy / Maranze Remodel—Financial, Portland, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 7:22)
    - Lipsitz-Basin Remodel, Portland, OR, 2006 (Box-folder 7:23-24)
    - Mahoney Project, Lake Oswego, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 7:25)
    - Margolin Project, Portland, OR, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 7:26-27)
    - Marian Abram's Children's Wing (MJCC), Portland, OR, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 7:28-36)
    - Marian Abram's Children's Wing (MJCC)—Electrical Submittals, Portland, OR, 1994 (Box-folder 7:37)
    - Marian Abram's Children's Wing (MJCC)—Project Manual, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 7:39)
    - Mark's Kitchen, 2007 (Box-folder 7:40)
    - McCarron Kitchen, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 7:41)
    - McTink [McCoy / Tinkle], Fairview, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 7:42-43)
    - Meadowlark Condominiums, Aloha, OR, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 7:44; 8:1-4)
    - Meadowlark Condominiums—Development Application, Aloha, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Merrill Property, 2001 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Metropolitan Presort, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Miller Addition, Portland, OR, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Minter Project, Newberg, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Mittleman Jewish Community Center—Financial, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Mittleman Jewish Community Center—Project Information, Portland, OR 1991 (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Morgan Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1986, 1998 (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Mowe Kitchen, Portland, OR, 1986 (Box-folder 8:13)
    - Mowe Westmoreland House, Portland, OR, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 8:14)
    - Multnomah Education Service District, Portland, OR, 1987 (Box-folder 8:15)
    - Murray Hill Eye Care, Beaverton, OR, 1987; 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8:16-20)
      Murray Hill Eyecare and Accent Eyewear are often combined in Webb's files. Therefore, Accent Eyewear should be viewed in conjunction with Murray Hill Eye Care.
    - Murray Hill Eye Care—Financial, Beaverton, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 8:21)
    - Mykelbust Remodel, Portland, OR, 2006 (Box-folder 8:22)
    - Nachtigal Residence, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 8:23)
    - Nakayama Garage, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:24)
    - Neal Steps and Greenhouse, 1980 (Box-folder 8:25)
    - Newhall Farmhouse, Sauvie Island,OR, 1988 (Box-folder 8:26)
    - Newhall Office, 1991 (Box-folder 8:27)
    - Northrup Project, Portland, OR, 1979 (Box-folder 8:28)
      Northrup was the name on the original folder; but no such name appears within the documents.
    - Ora and Bruce's Kitchen, 1999 (Box-folder 8:29)
    - Oregon Hydrocarbon, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:30)
    - Oregon Symphony Orchestra [Tenant Improvements], Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:31)
    - Pakman Cleaners, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 8:32)
    - Parcel "E," 1991 (Box-folder 8:33)
    - Parker House, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:34)
    - Port of Portland—Marketing, Portland, OR, c. 1989 (Box-folder 8:35)
    - Porter Renovation, Portland, OR, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 8:36)
    - Portis Renovations, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 8:37)
    - Portland All-Star Sports Project, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 8:38)
    - Portland Jewish Academy, Portland, OR, 1994 (Box-folder 8:39)
    - Portland Trolleycar Lofts, Portland, OR, 1996 (Box-folder 8:40)
    - Premier Press, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 8:41-42)
    - Prince Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 8:43)
    - Pyramid Storage, undated (Box-folder 8:44)
    - Quintana Kitchen, undated (Box-folder 8:45)
    - Rackner / Wolf Project, 1997 (Box-folder 8:46)
    - Raphael Kitchen Renovations, Portland, OR, 1997 (Box-folder 8:47-48)
    - Regional Design Images, 1993 (Box-folder 8:49)
    - Reich Remodel, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:50)
    - Reid House, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 8:51)
    - Reid House—Financials, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Rhine Project, Portland, OR, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Rhine Project—Communications, Portland, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Rhine Project—Non Standard Evidence, Portland, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Rhine Project—Petition for Review, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Rhine Project—Submitted Record Copy, Portland, OR, December 30, 1991 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Ritz Renovation, Tualatin, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Rock Creek Cleaners at Tanasbourne Village, 1993 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Rosenberg Renovations, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Rosenberg / Anderson Project, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Rosenberg / Lippman Project, Portland, OR, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 9:11-13)
    - Rosenthall Project, 2004 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Roseway House, Portland, OR, 2007 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Rystadt Apartments [Goose Hollow Neighbourhood], Portland, OR, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Salle / Forrest Project, Troutdale, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Sauvageau Project, Vancouver, WA, c. 1979 (Box-folder 9:18)
    - Schmand Bid [Estimate], Grays River, WA, undated (Box-folder 9:19)
    - Schwoerer Residence, Portland, OR, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9:20)
    - Schwoerer Residence—Phase II, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:21)
    - SE Division, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:22-24)
    - SE Division—Feasibility Study, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:25)
    - SE Division—Financial, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:26)
    - SE Division—Originals, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:27)
    - SE Division—Paste Ups, Portland, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 9:28)
    - Seiss / Sanchez Renovations, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 9:29)
    - Setrakian Residence, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:30)
    - Skyline Summit, Portland, OR, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 9:31-32)
    - Sobotnik Project, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 9:33)
    - Springridge—Background Information, Wilsonville, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:34)
      See also Charbonneau (French Prairie)
    - Springridge—Financials, Wilsonville, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:35)
    - Springridge—Golf Cart Storage: Communications, Wilsonville, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:36)
    - Springridge—Golf Cart Storage: Financial, Wilsonville, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:37)
    - Springridge—Golf Cart Storage: Planning Application, Wilsonville, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 9:38)
    - Springridge—Golf Cart Storage: Project Information, Wilsonville, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 9:39)
    - Springridge—Pool Enclosure: Communications, Wilsonville, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:40)
    - Springridge—Pool Enclosure: Financial, Wilsonville, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 9:41)
    - Springridge—Pool Enclosure: Project Information, Wilsonville, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:42)
    - Springridge—Product Brochures, Wilsonville, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 9:43)
    - Stearns Project, Vancouver, WA, 1993 (Box-folder 9:44)
    - Steward Feasibility, 1987 (Box-folder 9:45)
    - Stone / Moreland Kitchen Remodel, Portland, OR, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 9:46-47; 10:1)
    - Strange Kitchen, 2001 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Sukkot Project, Portland, OR, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Sylvia Beach Hotel, Newport, OR, undated (Box-folder 10:4)
      Not designed by Webb, but she helped with some aspects of the remodel.
    - Tanzer Project, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Taste of China, Lake Oswego, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Taste of China—Financial, Lake Oswego, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Taste of China—Julie Livingston's Notebook, Lake Oswego, OR, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Taylor Project, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Thomas Residential Addition, Newberg, OR, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Thompson Renovation, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Tinning Project, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Tuality Christian Center, Aloha, OR, 1996 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Two Barns Farm, Yamhill County, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 10:14-15)
    - Verity Homes [Empty Nest], 1993 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Veron Houseboat, Portland, OR, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Veron Houseboat Presentation, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 10:18)
    - Vranizan Attic Renovation, Portland, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Vranizan Attic Renovation—Financial, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Warm Springs Early Childhood Learning Center, Warm Springs, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 10:21)
    - Warm Springs Elder Care, Warm Springs, OR, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 10:22)
    - Warm Springs—Miscellaneous, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Box-folder 10:23)
    - Warm Springs—Richard Macy's Book, Warm Springs, OR, 1987 (Box-folder 10:24)
    - Wax Urban Arts Studio, Portland, OR, 2004 (Box-folder 10:25-28)
    - Webb Renovations, Florida, 1996 (Box-folder 10:29)
    - Weisberg Residence, 2000 (Box-folder 10:30)
    - West Village Construction, 1991 (Box-folder 10:31)
    - Whitney Renovations, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 10:32)
    - Willamette Print and Blueprint Co., Portland, OR, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 10:33-35)
    - Willis Garage / Carport, Portland, OR, 1996 (Box-folder 10:36)
    - Withycombe Project, 1979 (Box-folder 10:37)
      Project of "The Reconstruction Company"—ran by Pamela Webb and Fred Wood.
    - Wotipka Project, Portland, OR, 2000 (Box-folder 10:38)
    - Yamhill Project, 1979 (Box-folder 10:39)
- Non-structural Designs
  - Furnishings
    - Furniture—"The Rooster," 1995 (Box-folder 10:40)
    - Furniture [1993], n.d. (Map-case 34:12:1)
  - Art
    - Artwork, undated (Box-folder 10:41,, Oversize 15:1-5,, Map-case 33:13-15)
    - Artwork [On Metal], undated (Box-folder 10:42)
    - Artwork [On Plexiglas], undated (Box-folder 10:43)
    - Sketchbook(s), undated (Box 13-14,, Oversize 15:6)
- Photographs
  - Career Overview
    - Dossier Pictures, c. 2001 (Box-folder 10:44)
    - "Pam Webb—Architect," undated (Box-folder 10:45)
    - Models [Photographs of..], undated (Oversize 16:1)
  - Educational / Scholastic
    - "Architecture School" 1984-1985, 1991 (Box-folder 10:46)
  - Community Involvement
    - Fairmont Hotel, Portland, OR, 1980 (Box-folder 10:47)
    - Sapporo Pavilion [also called the Portland Pavilion], Sapporo, Japan, 1989 (Box-folder 10:48,, Oversize 16:14)
  - Business Ventures / Development Projects
    - Lloyd Center 8 Plex, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 10:49)
  - Proposals
    - Florence All Events Center, Florence, OR, 1991 (Box-folder 10:50)
    - "Indian Trails" Proposal, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Box-folder 10:51)
    - Marion County Family Court Proposal, Salem, OR, undated, c. 1992 (Box-folder 10:52)
    - Vancouver Clinic OB / GYN, Vancouver, WA, 1993 (Box-folder 10:53)
  - Projects
    - Unknown Pictures (from Projects), undated (Box-folder 10:54)
    - Unknown Project, undated (Box-folder 10:55)
    - Abrams / Ramirez Renovations, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box-folder 10:56)
    - Accent Eyewear / Murray Hill Eye Care, Hillsboro, OR, undated (Oversize 16:2)
    - Andreson Renovation [Before and After], Sauvie Island,OR, undated (Box-folder 10:57)
    - Austen Row, Portland, OR, 1991, undated (Box-folder 10:58; 11-1,, Oversize 16:3)
    - Barnes / Kinsey Renovation, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1992-1993 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Beckett and Stephens Renovation, West Linn, OR, 2001 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Beckham House, Lake Oswego, OR, undated, c. 1985-1987 (Box-folder 11:4,, Oversize 16:4)
    - Beling / Dougherty Offices, Las Vegas, NV, undated, c. 1995 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Benton County, Benton County, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Cable Village, Portland, OR, 1994, 1997, undated (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Cable Village—Pre-construction, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 16:5)
    - Center for Airport Management, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1995 (Box-folder 11:8,, Oversize 16:6)
    - Charbonneau [AKA French Prairie], Wilsonville, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:9,, Oversize 16:7)
      See Springridge files.
    - Claremont Clubhouse, Portland, OR, 1992, undated (Box-folder 11:10-11)
    - Cogan Deck, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 16:8)
    - Cogan Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:12)
    - East Bank, Portland, OR, 1995, undated, c. 1992 (Box-folder 11:13-14,, Oversize 16:9)
    - Epstein Project, Portland, OR, 2001 (Box-folder 11:15)
    - Ettinger Beach House, Lincoln City, OR, 1995, undated (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Forest Heights, Portland, OR, 1990-1991,1993, n.d. (Box-folder 11:17)
    - Forest Heights—Carney, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 11:18)
    - Forest Heights—"Issues to Resolve," Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 11:19)
    - Frazier Court, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:20)
    - Fredricksburg, Virginia House, undated (Box-folder 11:21,, Oversize 16:10)
    - Free Project, undated (Box-folder 11:22)
    - Garibaldi Beach House, Garibaldi, OR, 1993 (Box-folder 11:23)
    - Goldschmidt Office, Portland, OR, January, 1993 (Box-folder 11:24)
    - Gordon Beach House, Surf Pines, OR, undated, c. 2001 (Box-folder 11:25)
    - Graden Project, undated
    - Green / Holden Project, Portland, OR, n.d., c. 1984 (Box-folder 11:27)
    - Greenberg / Ritchie Project, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:28)
    - Greene Project, Seattle, WA, undated (Box-folder 11:29)
    - Griffith / Dickey Remodel, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:30)
    - Griffith / Dickey House II, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 11:31)
    - Hall Farmhouse Renovation, Troutdale, OR, 1996 (Box-folder 11:32)
    - Havurah Shalom, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:33)
    - Hearing / Lawshe Remodel, Portland, OR, 1993, undated (Box-folder 11:34,, Oversize 16:11)
    - Jumby Bay, undated (Box-folder 11:35)
    - Jung Addition, undated (Box-folder 11:36)
    - Kaer House, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:37)
    - Kalisvaart & Co., Portland, OR, undated, c. 1994 (Box-folder 11:38)
    - Kaye Cabin, Hood River, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:39)
    - Klapper / Hickey, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:40)
    - Koop House, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1991 (Box-folder 11:41)
    - Langford House, Portland, OR, 1994, undated (Box-folder 11:42-43)
    - Langford House—Tour, Portland, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 11:44)
    - Lansky Project, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box-folder 11:45)
    - Leland Project, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 16:12)
    - Levy / Maranze Remodel, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:46)
    - Lewis County Art Center, Lewis County, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:47)
    - Margolin Project, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 11:48)
    - Marian Abram's Children's Wing (MJCC), Portland, OR, 1995, undated (Box-folder 11:49-50,, Oversize 16:13)
    - McTink [McCoy / Tinkle], Fairview, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Miller Addition, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Morgan Kitchen / Deck, Portland, OR, undated, c. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Murray Hill Eye Care, Beaverton, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Nachtigal Residence, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Newhall Farmhouse, Sauvie Island,OR, undated (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Parker House, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Port of Portland—Marketing, undated (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Porter Renovation, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Portis Renovations, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:10)
    - Pyramid Storage, undated (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Reich Remodel, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:12)
    - Ritz Renovation, Tualatin, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:13)
    - Rock Creek Cleaners at Tanasbourne Village, 1993 (Box-folder 12:14)
    - Schwoerer Residence, Portland, OR, December 1, 1992, undated (c. 1992-1993) (Box-folder 12:15-16)
    - SE Division, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:17)
    - Seaside City Hall, Seaside, OR, 1990 (Box-folder 12:18)
    - Skyline Summit, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:19)
    - Springridge, Wilsonville, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:20-21)
    - Steward Feasibility, 1987 (Box-folder 12:22)
    - Taste of China, Lake Oswego, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:23,, Oversize 16:15)
    - Thompson Renovation, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:24)
    - Tuality Christian Center, Aloha, OR, 1995 (Box-folder 12:25)
    - Two Barns Farm, Yamhill County, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:26-29,, Oversize 16:16)
    - Veron Houseboat, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:30)
    - Vranizan Attic Renovation, Portland, OR, 1992 (Box-folder 12:31)
    - Warm Springs Early Childhood—Promo, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:32)
    - Warm Springs Early Childhood Learning Center and Warm Springs Elder Care, Warm Springs, OR undated (Box-folder 12:33)
    - Warm Springs Elder Care, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:34)
    - Warm Springs—Miscellaneous, Warm Springs, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:35,, Oversize 16:17-18)
    - Whitney Renovations, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:36)
    - Willamette Print and Blueprint, Portland, OR, 1994, 1998 (Box-folder 12:37)
    - Willis Garage / Carport, Portland, OR, undated (Box-folder 12:38)
  - Non-structural Designs
    - Furniture, undated, 1987, 1992 (Box-folder 12:39-40)
    - Jewelry, undated (Box-folder 12:41)
- Oversized Architectural Drawings
  - Educational / Scholastic
    - School Work—Graphics, Portland, OR, 1982 (Map-case 34:12:2-4)
    - School Work—Oregon School of Design, undated, c. 1982, c. 1984 (Map-case 34:12:5-7)
    - "Student Work," 1982 (Oversize 19:1,, Oversize 32-36)
  - Community Involvement
    - Fairmont Hotel, Beaverton, OR, 1986, undated (Oversize 19:2-3)
  - Business Ventures / Development Projects
    - 2725 SE 34th Street, Portland, OR, 1993 (Map-case 34:1:1)
    - Scheller / Webb Townhouse Project, 66th Street, undated (Oversize 19:4)
  - Miscellaneous Maps and Plans
    - Central Westside Map of Portland, Portland,OR, undated (Oversize 37)
    - Miscellaneous plan-Louisville Waterway Master Plan, 1991 (Oversize 17:1)
      Plan not created by Webb. Master Plan Created by Hargreaves and Associates—with whom Webb collaborated during the East Bank Master Plan.
    - Topographic Surveys, undated (Oversize 38)
  - Proposals
    - Digital Equiptment Corporation, Tualatin, OR, 1992 (Map-case 34:1:2)
    - Portland Community College Proposal, Portland, OR, undated (Oversize 17:3)
  - Projects
    - Untitled Project, undated (Oversize 17:4)
    - Untitled Project, undated (Oversize 17:5)
      May relate to Skloot.
    - Untitled Project, 1982 (Map-case 34:1:3)
    - Untitled Project, 1982 (Map-case 34:1:4)
    - Miscellaneous Untitled / Unknown Drawings / Designs, undated (Oversize 17:6-16; 18:1-4,, Map-case 34:1:5-11; 34:13:1)
      Materials include one dated site plan from 1989.
    - Miscellaneous Drawings / Renderings [on Foam board], undated (Map-case 34:1:12)
    - Abrams / Ramirez Renovations, Portland, OR, 1996 (Oversize 19:5-6)
    - Acadia Properties, Bend, OR, undated (Oversize 19:7)
    - Accent Eyewear / Murray Hill Eye Care, Hillsboro, OR / Beaverton, OR, 1993 (Oversize 19:8,, Map-case 34:1:13)
      The drawings for these two eye care centers were intermingled by Webb and often lack distinquishing titles.
    - Alden / Drummond Residence, Portland, OR 1986 (Map-case 34:13:2)
    - Anderson Webb Properties—House, Portland, OR, 1993 (Map-case 34:1:14)
    - Andreson Renovation, Sauvie Island,OR, 1994, 1996, undated (Oversize 19:9-10,, Map-case 34:1:15)
    - Aspenridge, Vancouver, WA, 1991 (Map-case 34:1:16; 34:13:3)
    - Auditor's Office, Portland, OR, 1993, 1994, undated (Oversize 19:11-12,, Map-case 34:1:17-19)
    - Austen Row, Portland, OR, 1989, 1990, undated (Oversize 19:13-15; 20:1,, Map-case 34:1:20-21)
    - Balderas Renovation, undated (Oversize 20:2)
    - Barnes / Kinsey Renovation, Portland, OR, 1992 (Oversize 20:3,, Map-case 34:2:1-2)
    - Barringan Residence, Portland, OR, 1993 (Oversize 20:4,, Map-case 34:2:3)
    - Beck Residence, Napa, CA, undated (Oversize 20:5)
    - Beckett and Stephens Renovation, West Linn, OR, 1992, 2001-2002, undated (Oversize 20:6, Map-case 34:2:4)
    - Beckham House, Lake Oswego, OR, 1985, undated (Oversize 20:7,, Map-case 34:2:5; 34:13:4)
    - Beling / Dougherty Offices, Las Vegas, NV, 1995, undated (Oversize 20:8-9,, Map-case 34:2:6)
    - Belvoir Renovations, Portland, OR, 1997-1998 (Oversize 20:10-11)
    - Benson Residence, Portland, OR, 1985 (Oversize 20:12)
    - Bentley Renovation, Portland, OR. 1998, undated (Oversize 20:13, Map-case 34:2:7)